Guide to the Alfred Corn Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Alfred Corn papers
1961-2007
YCAL MSS 605
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
46
(65 boxes)
The collection consists of correspondence, writings, photographs, audiovisual material, and printed material, documenting aspects of Alfred Corn's work as a poet and writer as well as his relationships with other poets and writers.
Corn, Alfred, 1943-
General note
This finding aid describes a collection that has been acquired by the library in discrete segments over time. The narrative sections of the finding aid provide information about the content and context of the collection. The Collection Contents section provides a general description and in some instances a box or folder listing of the various acquisitions of the collection. The Processing Notes section provides information about the way and extent to which the library has processed this collection. The Arrangement section provides information about how material within this collection is organized and tips on how to locate material across various acquisitions.
General note
This collection has multiple call numbers. To page materials, please submit the Uncat call number for the appropriate acquisition along with the desired box number.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Alfred Corn, 1991-2011, and Glenn Horowitz Bookseller, 2007-2012.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 43A and 52 (computer disks): Original computer disks are restricted. Copies of electronic files are available through Access Services.
Alfred Corn (1943-)
Alfred Corn was born in Bainbridge, Georgia, in 1943. He received his B.A. in French Literature from Emory University in 1965 and his M.A. in French Literature from Columbia University in 1967. His books of poetry include: All Roads at Once (1976), A Call in the Midst of the Crowd (1978), The Various Light (1980), Notes from a Child of Paradise (1984), The West Door (1988), Autobiographies (1992), Present (1997), and Contradictions (2002). His other published books include a novel, Part of His Story (1997), a collection of critical essays, The Metamorphoses of Metaphor (1989), a study of prosody, The Poem's Heartbeat (1997), and a work of art criticism, Aaron Rose Photographs (2001). Corn has also been a frequent contributor to The New York Times Book Review and The Nation, and has written art criticism for Art in America and ARTnews magazines.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of correspondence, writings, photographs, audiovisual material, computer disks, and printed material, documenting aspects of Alfred Corn's work as a poet and writer as well as his relationships with other poets and writers.
Arrangement
Organized into twelve groupings: I. July 1991 Acquisition, 1964-1988. II. September 1996 Acquisition, undated. III. April 1999 Acquisition, 1996-1998, undated. IV. April 1999 Acquisition, undated. V. November 2003 Acquisition, 1968-1989. VI. September 2004 Acquisition, 1969-2001. VII. September 2004 Acquisition, undated.VIII. September 2004 Acquisition, undated. IX. October 2007 Acquisition, 1994-2007. X. November 2010 Acquisition, 1948-2010. XI. August 2011 Acquisition, 1984-1990. XII. January 2012 Acquisition, 1989-1999.
Material within this collection has been organized by acquisition reflecting the fact that the collection has been acquired in increments over time.
Researchers should note that material within each acquisition overlaps with and/or relates to material found in other acquisitions. For instance, correspondence and writings can be found in most, if not all, of the groupings. In order to locate all relevant material within this collection, researchers will need to consult each acquisition described in the Collection Contents section.
Researchers should also note that similar material can be arranged differently in each acquisition, depending on how the material was organized when it was received by the library.
American literature -- 20th Century; American poetry -- 20th Century; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Poets, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Electronic documents; Sound recordings; Video recordings; Corn, Alfred, 1943-
- July 1991 Acquisition, 1964-1988; 1; 9.5; (17 boxes)
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Purchased from Alfred Corn on the George B. Alvord Fund, Danford N. Barney, Jr. Fund, and the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, 1991.
  Arrangement
  Organized into six subgroupings: Correspondence, Writings, Writings of Others, Personal Papers, Printed Material, and Oversize.
  Scope and Contents
  This portion of the collection includes manuscripts of works by Corn, such as All Roads at Once, Various Light, and The West Door; manuscripts by John Hollander, James Merrill, Richard Wilbur; anthologies with works by Corn; periodicals; small press publications; correspondence with Elizabeth Bishop, Eleanor Clarke, Robert Fitzgerald, John Hersey and others; and correspondence and writings related to the book edited by Corn, Incarnation: contemporary writers on the New Testament (New York: Viking, 1990).
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 204
  - Correspondence
    - "A" General (Box 1)
    - Academy of American Poets, 1983-1988 (Box 1)
    - Appleman, Philip, 1975-1981 (Box 1)
    - Arvio Sarah, 1984-1988 (Box 1)
    - Ashbery, John, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Austin, David Craig, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 1)
    - "B" General, 2 (Box 1)
    - Bishop, Elizabeth, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
    - Bloom, Harold, 1975-1976; 2 (Box 1)
    - Bogen, Don, 1984-1988 (Box 1)
    - Bradley, George, 1984-1988 (Box 1)
    - Brainard, Joe, 1983 (Box 1)
    - Brodsky, Joseph, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Bromwich, David, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Brown, Walter, 1971-1984; 6 (Box 1)
    - Brutus, Dennis, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Buechner, Frederick, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
    - "C" General (Box 1)
    - Clampitt, Amy, 1988; 2 (Box 1)
    - Cole, Henri, 1980-1988; 7 (Box 1)
    - Conarroe, Joel, 1978-1981; 2 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut College, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Cooper, Jane, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Conroy, Frank, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Corn, Alfred, Outgoing Correspondence, 1964-1988; 17 (Box 1)
      Letters from Alfred Corn to Mr. & Mrs. A. D. Corn, Jr., David Kalstone, James Merrill, and other unidentified recipients
    - Crase, Douglas, 1977-1988; 2 (Box 1)
    - Cronorama, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
    - Cummington Press, 1986 (Box 1)
    - "D" General (Box 1)
    - Danforth, Ted, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
    - Davenport, Guy, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Davies, Robertson, 1988 March 29 (Box 1)
    - Des Pres, Terrence, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Dillard, Annie (Box 1)
    - Dove, Rita, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Dubus, Andre, 1989 March 17 (Box 1)
    - "E" General (Box 1)
    - Erdrich, Louise, 1988 (Box 1)
    - "F" General (Box 1)
    - Feldman, Irving, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
    - Fitzgerald, Penny, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
    - Fitzgerald, Robert, 1977-1980; 3 (Box 1)
    - Flanders, Tamzen, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Folkman, Jonathan, 1981-1985 (Box 1)
    - Fontanella, Luigi, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
    - Fowles, Elizabeth, 1988 April 10 (Box 1)
    - Francis, H. E., 1975-1986 (Box 1)
    - Fugard, Athol, 1988 (Box 1)
    - "G" General (Box 1)
    - Galassi, Jonathan, 1989 January 27 (Box 1)
    - George Mason University, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
    - Georgia Review, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
    - Gioia, Michael Dana, 1978-1989; 2 (Box 1)
    - Gordon, Mary, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
    - Gray, Francine, 1978-1981 (Box 1)
    - Greene, Graham, 1988 May 18 (Box 1)
    - Gunn, Thom, 1981-1988; 2 (Box 1)
    - "H" General (Box 1)
    - Haas, Bob, 1989 August 8 (Box 1)
    - Hadas, Rachel, 1984-1988; 2 (Box 1)
    - Hainley, Bruce, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
    - Hall, Daniel, 1983-1988; 7 (Box 1)
    - Hammer, Lanny, 1978-1985; 5 (Box 1)
    - Hawkins, Peter, 1979-1988; 3 (Box 1)
    - Heaney, Seamus, 1988 April 5 (Box 1)
    - Hecht, Anthony, 1978-1988; 3 (Box 1)
    - Hersey, John, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Hewitt, Andrew, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Hill, Geoffrey, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Hine, Daryl, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
    - Hollander, John, 1975-1988; 5 (Box 2)
    - Howard, Richard, 1971-1987; 3 (Box 2)
    - Howes, Barbara, 1979-1988; 2 (Box 2)
    - Hudson Review, 1979-1984; 4 (Box 2)
    - Humphreys, Jo, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
    - Ingram Merrill Foundation, 1974-1981 (Box 2)
    - "J" General (Box 2)
    - Jackson, David, 1982-1988 (Box 2)
    - Jacobsen, Josephine, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Jacoff, Rachel, 1974-1978 (Box 2)
    - Jones, Ann, 1970-1988; 25 (Box 2)
    - "K" General (Box 2)
    - Kalstone, David, 1972-1982; 4 (Box 2)
    - Karlinsky, Simon, 1973-1988; 15 (Box 2)
    - Kennedy, William, 1988 March 30 (Box 2)
    - Kenyon Review, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
    - "L" General (Box 2)
    - Lehman, David, 1979-1988; 2 (Box 2)
    - Leibowitz, Herb, 1977-1979 (Box 2)
    - Leithauser, Brad, 1984-1988; 4 (Box 2)
    - Library of Congress, 1979-1982 (Box 2)
    - L'Heureux, John, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
    - Logan, William, 1981-1988; 7 (Box 2)
    - Lynch, Michael, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
    - "M" General, 2 (Box 2)
    - Malone, Michael, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Mars-Jones, Adam, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
    - Martin, Robert, 1977-1988; 4 (Box 2)
    - McClatchy, J. D., 1975-1986; 5 (Box 2)
    - McClatchy, J. D., 1986; 2 (Box 3)
    - McCorkle, James, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - McCourt, James, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - McCourt, James, 1983-1988; 6 (Box 3)
    - McPherson, Sandra, 1984-1988; 2 (Box 3)
    - Mendelson, Edward, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
    - Merrill, James, 1973-1988; 16 (Box 3)
    - Merwin, William, 1979-1988; 3 (Box 3)
    - Meyer, Thomas, 1977-1986; 14 (Box 3)
    - Middlebrook, Diane, 1974-1988; 3 (Box 3)
    - Milosz, Czeslaw, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Monette, Paul, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Moore, Paul, 1988 October 25 (Box 3)
    - Murdoch, Iris, 1988 (Box 3)
    - "N" General (Box 3)
    - The Nation, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Nemerov, Howard, 1974-1978 (Box 3)
    - New England Review (Box 3)
    - New Republic, 1986 (Box 3)
    - New York Review of Books, 1979 (Box 3)
    - New York Times Book Review, 1988 (Box 3)
    - New Yorker, 1973-1980 (Box 3)
    - Nims, John, 1982-1987 (Box 3)
    - "O" General (Box 3)
    - O'Connor, Flannery, 1962 (Box 3)
    - "P" General, 3 (Box 3)
    - Parini, Jay, 1984-1988 (Box 3)
    - Paris Review, 1978-1983 (Box 3)
    - Park, Darragh, 1978-1984 (Box 3)
    - Parnassus: Poetry in Review, 1976-1979 (Box 3)
    - Percy, Walker, 1988 March 20 (Box 3)
    - Peréngi, Eleanor, 1978-1987; 2 (Box 3)
    - Pettingell, Phoebe, 1978-1988 (Box 3)
    - Pinsky, Robert, 1977-1987; 11 (Box 3)
    - Plante, David, 1986-1988 (Box 3)
    - Poem, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Poetry, 1974-1982; 4 (Box 3)
    - Poetry Center, 1977-1986 (Box 3)
    - Poets On, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Powers, J. F., 1988 September 19 (Box 3)
    - Price, Reynolds, 1988-1990 (Box 3)
    - Quarterly Review of Literature, 1977-1988 (Box 3)
    - Quilligan, Maureen, 1983 (Box 3)
    - "R" General (Box 3)
    - Robinson, Marilynne, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Rorem, Ned, 1979-1987 (Box 3)
    - Rosenberg, David, 1983-1987 (Box 3)
    - "S" General, 3 (Box 3)
    - Sacks, Peter, 1979-1987; 2 (Box 3)
    - Salter, Mary Jo, 1984-1987; 5 (Box 3)
    - Salter, Mary Jo, 1987-1988; 6 (Box 4)
    - Sandy, Stephen, 1983-1985; 4 (Box 4)
    - Schnadrenberg, Trude, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Schulman, Grace, 1977-1988; 7 (Box 4)
    - Shaw, Robert B., 1982-1989; 5 (Box 4)
    - Seshadri, Vijay, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
    - Shore, Jane, 1985-1987; 3 (Box 4)
    - Sifton, Elisabeth, 1977-1979 (Box 4)
    - Silk, Dennis, 1984-1988 (Box 4)
    - Smith, David, 1980-1985; 2 (Box 4)
    - Southwest Review, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Spark, Muriel, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Stevens, Holly, 1978-1988 (Box 4)
    - Stevenson, Anne, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
    - Stivender, David, 1986-1988; 2 (Box 4)
    - "T" General (Box 4)
    - Temkina, Marina, 1988; 2 (Box 4)
    - Thomas, R. S., 1988 November 4 (Box 4)
    - Threepenny Review, 1988 March 22 (Box 4)
    - Tillinghast, Richard, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
    - Trevor, William, 1988 August 1 (Box 4)
    - "U" General (Box 4)
    - Ulacia, Manuel, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
    - Updike, John, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
    - "V" General (Box 4)
    - Vendler, Helen, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
    - Vaill, Amanda, 1988 April 1 (Box 4)
    - Viking Penguin Inc., 1988; 2 (Box 4)
    - Virga, Vincent, 1985-1988 (Box 4)
    - "W" General (Box 4)
    - Warner, Marina, 1987-1988; 4 (Box 4)
    - Warren, Eleanor Clark, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, 1980 September 7 (Box 4)
    - Warren, Rosanna, 1977-1988; 6 (Box 4)
    - Welty, Eudora, 1978-1988; 2 (Box 4)
    - White, Edmund, 1968-1988; 18 (Box 4)
    - Whittemore, Reed, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Wilbur, Richard, 1976-1988; 3 (Box 4)
    - Wilcox, Pat, 1972-1975; 10 (Box 4)
    - Wildes, Doretta, 1979-1988; 7 (Box 4)
    - Williams, A. Claude, 1974-1977; 3 (Box 4)
    - Williams, Jonathan, 1977-1980 (Box 4)
    - Williamson, Alan, 1978-1981; 4 (Box 4)
    - Wilson, A. N., 1988 (Box 4)
    - Woiwode, Larry, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
    - Wojahn, David, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
    - Wright, Charles, 1976-1988; 2 (Box 4)
    - "Y" General (Box 4)
    - Yenser, Stephen, 1977-1988; 6 (Box 5)
    - ---, Deborah, 1988 (Box 5)
    - ---, Kenward, 1982 (Box 5)
    - ---, Stephen, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
    - Unidentified, 1976-1988; 7 (Box 5)
  - Writings
    - All Roads At Once, 1976-1977; 6 (Box 6)
      Includes typescripts, corrected galleys, bound proofs, and reviews
    - Book reviews, 1962-1972; 3 (Box 6)
    - A Call in the Midst of the Crowd, circa 1976; 2 (Box 6)
      Includes notes, autograph manuscript, and typescript
    - A Call in the Midst of the Crowd, circa 1978; 5 (Box 7)
      Includes typescripts, corrected galleys, and reviews
    - Le Cid: translation from Act I, typescript (Box 7)
    - The Column, printed version, 1980 (Box 7)
    - "Country Hosts," typescript (Box 7)
    - "Da u Album," photocopy of typescript (Box 7)
    - Dead Reckoning, typescript, 1976 October (Box 7)
    - "The Documentary Goes Full-Length," photocopy of printed version, 1972 May 20 (Box 7)
    - "The Doorman," typescript (Box 7)
    - "Michaux and the Organic," thesis, photocopy of typescript (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous poems, typescript, 2 (Box 7)
    - Navidad, St. Nicholas Ave, printed version, 1984 (Box 8)
    - "The New Life," printed version, 1983 (Box 8)
    - "New Year," printed version, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Notes from a Child of Paradise, 1983-1985; 5 (Box 8)
      Includes typescripts, bound proof, and reviews
    - Notes from a Child of Paradise, 1983-1984; 2 (Box 9)
      Includes book contract and promotional material
    - "The Notion of the Avant-Garde," photocopy of printed version, 1970 December (Box 9)
    - "Parables," autograph manuscript, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Preface to Incarnation: Contemporary Writers on the New Testament, typescript (Box 9)
    - "Radical Continuities," photocopy of printed version (Box 9)
    - "Romance American Style," typescript (Box 9)
    - Several Nights without Sleep, typescript (Box 9)
    - Somerset Alcaics, printed version, 1988 (Box 9)
    - "Sonnet I," autograph manuscript (Box 9)
    - Tongues on Trees, 1981-1983; 2 (Box 9)
      Includes printed version and invoice
    - "Townscape in December," photocopy of typescript (Box 9)
    - Travel journal, typescript, 1985 (Box 9)
    - The Various Light, 1979-1981; 6 (Box 9)
      Includes author's galleys, proofs, typescripts, and reviews
    - The West Door, corrected typescript, 1 (Box 9)
    - The West Door, 9 (Box 10)
      Includes corrected typescripts, bound proof, and spine copies
    - An Xmas Murder, printed version, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Untitled poem, typescript (Box 10)
  - Writings of Others
    - Bidart, Frank, The Sacrifice, typescript, 1980; 2 (Box 10)
    - Bloom, Harold, "Harold Bloom on Poetry," New Republic, photocopy of printed version, 1976 November 20 (Box 10)
    - Buechner, Frederick, "First Corinthians," corrected typescript, undated (Box 10)
    - Butor, Michel, "Le Rêve de Prague," typescript, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Crase, Douglas, The Revisionist, typescript, undated (Box 11)
    - Davenport, Guy, "II Timothy," typescript, undated (Box 11)
    - Fitzgerald, Robert, Translation of Aeneis IV, typescript, undated (Box 11)
    - Galassi, Jonathan, "A Prisoner of Christ," corrected typescript, undated (Box 11)
    - Hersey, John, "Revelation," typescript, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Hine, Daryl, "Scenes from Country Life," typescript, undated (Box 11)
    - Hollander, John, Powers of Thirteen, typescript, 1978 November 21 (Box 11)
    - Howard, Richard, Translation of The Flowers of Evil by Charles Baudelaire, typescript, undated (Box 11)
    - Howard, Richard, "Homage" and "Beyond Words," typescripts, undated (Box 11)
    - McClatchy, J. D., [Two Poems], corrected typescript, undated (Box 11)
    - McPherson, Sandra, Streamers, typescript, undated (Box 11)
    - Merrill, James (Box 11)
      - "The Changing Light at Sandoven," typescript, undated (Box 11)
      - "Days of 1941 and 1944," and an address given at Washington University, corrected typescript, undated (Box 11)
    - Morgan, Frederick, "The Fountain and Other Fables," typescript, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Pinsky, Robert (Box 11)
      - An Explanation of America, typescript, 1978 (Box 11)
      - History of My Heart, typescript, 1983 (Box 11)
      - "Jesus and Isolt," corrected typescript, 1988 April 12 (Box 11)
    - Plante, David, "St. Paul's Epistle to the Romans," corrected typescript, undated (Box 12)
    - Rosenberg, David, [Five Pieces], typescript, 1982 February 18 (Box 12)
    - Salter, Mary Jo (Box 12)
      - "In Other Kingdoms," typescript, 1985 (Box 12)
      - Introduction for Alfred Corn reading at Mount Holyoke College, typescript, 1985 (Box 12)
      - Unfinished Painting, typescript, undated (Box 12)
    - Schulman, Grace (Box 12)
      - Hemispheres, typescript, undated (Box 12)
      - "Jude, Not Obscure," corrected typescript, undated (Box 12)
    - Shore, Jane, The Minute Hand, typescript, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Wilbur, Richard, translation of Phaedra, typescript, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Wilcox, Patricia, Comforts of the Sun, typescript, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Woidoe, Larry, Acts, The Church Set Free, corrected typescript, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Yenser, Stephen, [Poems], typescript, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Unidentified author, [Poems], typescript, 1978; 3 (Box 12)
  - Personal Papers
    Conditions Governing Access
    Box 43 contains audiovisual material. Restricted access. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Applications for Guggenheim, 1977-1981 (Box 13)
    - Certificate for NEA Literature Fellowship, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Program from the White House: "A Salute to Poetry and American Poets", 1980 (Box 13)
    - Discovery / The Nation Poetry Prize, announcement of the winners, 1980-1986; 2 (Box 13)
    - Leonore Marshall / Nation Poetry Prize, 1983-1984; 2 (Box 13)
      Includes announcement of open nominations and other materials
    - Citation from the American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1983 (Box 13)
    - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, programs for ceremonial and exhibition, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Invitation to the presentation of the Common Wealth Award [to Christopher Isherwood], 1983 (Box 13)
    - Poetry Society of America, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
      Includes programs for the 74th Annual Awards Ceremony and 1983 membership list
    - The Lamont Poetry Selection, announcements of contest, 1987-1989; 2 (Box 13)
    - Academy of American Poets, 1983-1985; 6 (Box 13)
      Includes two invitations from Ed Koch, 50th anniversary poster, a tribute to W. H. Auden, calendar of readings, and other materials
    - Connecticut Poetry Circuit, itinerary, 1980 (Box 13)
    - The Poetry Center, 1977-1989; 8 (Box 13)
      Includes calendar of events and other promotional materials
    - 1st New York Poetry Marathon, 1981 April (Box 13)
    - The Library of Congress, literary events calendar, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
    - City College of New York, 17th Annual Spring Poetry Festival, 1984 April 27 (Box 13)
    - Celebration '86: 10th Anniversary of the Glines, 1986 June (Box 13)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation: Announcement of Fellowship Competition United States and Canada, 1988 (Box 13)
    - New York Public Library: A Memorial Tribute to David Kalstone, 1986 September 20; 2 (Box 13)
    - Various readings, undated; 2 (Box 13)
    - Columbia University, 1983-1985; 2 (Box 13)
      Includes poster for the writing program and graduate writing program syllabus
    - The Writer's Voice, calendar of classes, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
    - Passports, 1967-1977 (Box 13)
    - Publicity photograph, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Planners, 1973-1975; 3 (Box 13)
    - Planners, 1976-1980; 2 (Box 14)
    - Frankly Speaking: "Poetry: Writing It, Teaching It, Publishing It". Klappert/Corn/Nelson, 1982 January 17; 1; 00:43:43; There is a high amount of hum and background noise on the tape. (Box 43, Item barcode 39002099362718)
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      This program was out of George Mason University.
    - Yale Reading. Bloom/Corn/Ashberry, 1976 April 20; 1; 01:13:12; The program is distorted at times. (Box 43, Item barcode 39002099362726)
    - Biographical material, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Clipping, undated (Box 14)
    - Interview for Cracklings, 1977 December 28 (Box 14)
    - Inventory, undated (Box 14)
    - Photographs, circa 1968-1982; 2 (Box 14)
    - Scrapbooks, circa 1961; 2 (Box 14)
    - Report cards, 1949-1956 (Box 15)
    - Valdosta High School, 1961 (Box 15)
    - Midterm take-home exam, Greek 125, Yale University, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Printed Material
    - American Book Review, 1985 (Box 15)
    - The Amicus Journal, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
    - Art & Antiques, 1985 May (Box 15)
    - Boston Review, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
    - Chiaroscuro, 1961 (Box 15)
    - Christopher Street, 1978 May (Box 15)
    - Connecticut Artists, 1980 (Box 15)
    - Cracklings, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Fallout, 1961 or 1962 (Box 15)
    - Forthcoming: Jewish Imaginative Writing, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
    - Gay Sunshine: A Journal of Gay Liberation, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Harbinger: The Journal of Social Ecology, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1984 Aug (Box 15)
    - The Nation, 1975-1986; 2 (Box 15)
    - The National Book Critics Circle Journal, 1985 January 1 (Box 15)
    - The New Leader Christmas Book Issue, 1978 December 4 (Box 15)
    - The New Republic, 1977-1987; 2 (Box 15)
    - The New Yorker, 1975-1986; 2 (Box 15)
    - New York Native, 1986-1988; 3 (Box 15)
    - The New York Review of Books, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1977-1988 (Box 15)
    - The New York Times, Travel section, 1988 November 20 (Box 15)
    - Paris Match, 1968 May 18
    - Poem, 1972-1976 (Box 15)
    - Poetry, 1977 January (Box 16)
    - Poetry Nation Review, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Poetry Pilot, 1983-1988 (Box 16)
    - Poetry Society of America Newsletter, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Poet's Audio Center catalog (Box 16)
    - Saturday Review, 1972-1985 (Box 16)
    - The Threepenny Review, 1987-1988 (Box 16)
    - University Publishing, 1978 (Box 16)
    - Vanity Fair, 1983 August (Box 16)
    - Voice: Literary Supplement, 1988 (Box 16)
    - The Viking Press catalog, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Washington Post Book World, 1979-1982 (Box 16)
    - Writer's, 1988 December (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
  - Oversize
    - The Column, 1980 (Box 17 (Oversize))
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1977-1988 (Box 17 (Oversize))
    - Paris Match, 1968 May 18 (Box 17 (Oversize))
- September 1996 Acquisition, undated; 2; 9; (9 boxes)
  Purchased from Alfred Corn on the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, 1996.